## **EDMARK TUAZON**

Cavite, Philippines · 09707688781/09675109949

edmark.softdev@gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/edmarktuazon/



I' am self-taught, freelance/part-time Frontend Web Developer based in Cavite, Philippines I specialized in Frontend Web Development. I'm focus on creating responsive, and user-friendly websites, I use the latest frontend technologies to bring my client visions to project. I'm dedicated to providing good quality solutions that meet the needs and goals of my clients, as a self-taught Frontend Web Developer, I honed my skills through continuous learning and exploring.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**FEBRUARY 2022 - PRESENT** 

# **PROJECT BASED JR. FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER,** TEMHOLIX COMMMUNICATION DESIGN INC.

- Build responsive and user-friendly websites for individuals, groups, startups, and small businesses.
- Converting UI/UX Designs into responsive Web Pages using latest Frontend
  Technologies (HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript and PHP)
- Implementing clean code, test, report, and debug operations in the User Interface.
- Identifying and fixing website problems, including broken links, typographical errors, and UI responsive issues.
- Handling FTP client for uploading in every done project and for UI Testing
- Collaborate with team lead using GitHub

**JULY 2021 - PRESENT** 

# FREELANCE/PART-TIME FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, FIVERR AND OUTSIDE FIVERR

- Converting UI/UX Designs into responsive Web Pages using latest Frontend
  Technologies (HTML5, CSS3/SCSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript and PHP)
- Editing existing website of my client and supporting client's needs after a project

#### **EDUCATION**

**JUNE 2020 - JULY 2023** 

**2YEARS ASSOCIATE DEGREE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY,** IMUS COMPUTER COLLEGE, CAVITE

**JUNE 2018 – APRIL 2020** 

K TO 12 SCIENCE TECHNOLOGY ENGINEERING AND MATHEMATICS (STRAND),

SAINT JUDE PARISH SCHOOL, CAVITE

**JUNE 14 - APRIL 2018** 

SECONDARY EDUCATION, TRECE MARTIRES CITY NATIONAL HIGHSCHOOL, CAVITE

**JUNE 2008 - APRIL 2014** 

PRIMARY EDUCATION, BAGOONG POOK ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, CAVITE

### TECHNICAL SKILLS AND QUALIFICATION

- HTML5
- CSS3/SCSS
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap 4/5
- JavaScript

- jQuery
- Vue.js
- Basic PHP
- Adobe XD
- Figma

#### **INTERNSHIP**

**SEPTEMBER 25, 2021 - FEBRUARY 22, 2022** 

#### FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, LINKHELPERS INTERNATIOANAL INC.

- Completed 300 hours of On-the-job training remotely
- Created mockup using Figma and converted into responsive Web Page
- Worked on alternative Database server backend API
- Project done: <a href="https://freebibleph.com/">https://freebibleph.com/</a>

https://task-place.vercel.app/

### **AWARD AND CERTIFICATE**

• Certificate of completion - On-the-job training

LinkHelper International Inc.

S.Y 2022 - 2023

• 1<sup>st</sup> Runner up Award - Web Development Competition

Imus Computer College, Cavite 2022